<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <SylvieRace_Finally.label>Endland Outfit</SylvieRace_Finally.label>
  <SylvieRace_Finally.description>This appears to be an old man's clothing — it doesn't seem like something from this world.</SylvieRace_Finally.description>
  <SylvieRace_FineClothing.label>Black dress</SylvieRace_FineClothing.label>
  <SylvieRace_FineClothing.description>A solemn and elegant black dress — wearing it should look very graceful, and it would be well-suited for formal occasions.</SylvieRace_FineClothing.description>
  <SylvieRace_Kimono.label>Kimono</SylvieRace_Kimono.label>
  <SylvieRace_Kimono.description>A fully-wrapped kimono outfit; its warm color tones give it an adorable feel. During festivals, many people are sure to be seen wearing one.</SylvieRace_Kimono.description>
  <SylvieRace_MaidOutfit.label>Maid Outfit</SylvieRace_MaidOutfit.label>
  <SylvieRace_MaidOutfit.description>A maid outfit.</SylvieRace_MaidOutfit.description>
  <SylvieRace_ElegantClothing.label>Elegant Clothing</SylvieRace_ElegantClothing.label>
  <SylvieRace_ElegantClothing.description>The classic staff uniform, typically issued to service personnel. It's just... it might be a bit tight.</SylvieRace_ElegantClothing.description>
  <SylvieRace_HeavyMaid.label>Heavy Maid Outfit</SylvieRace_HeavyMaid.label>
  <SylvieRace_HeavyMaid.description>A maid outfit fastened with numerous ribbons and layered many times over. Its heavy, substantial feel provides a sense of comfort and security.</SylvieRace_HeavyMaid.description>
  <SylvieRace_StudentUniform.label>Student Uniform</SylvieRace_StudentUniform.label>
  <SylvieRace_StudentUniform.description>A thin sailor uniform brimming with the colors of youth. But in this world, there doesn't seem to be a requirement for standardized uniforms — so it's probably just worn for the sake of looking good.</SylvieRace_StudentUniform.description>
  <SylvieRace_Suits.label>Suit</SylvieRace_Suits.label>
  <SylvieRace_Suits.description>An outfit that exudes a sense of seriousness, generally reserved for management. Yet, for some inexplicable reason, it stirs an intense desire in peop</SylvieRace_Suits.description>
  <SylvieRace_Cheongsam.label>Cheongsam</SylvieRace_Cheongsam.label>
  <SylvieRace_Cheongsam.description>A purple qipao; although the slit isn't particularly high, it still stirs the imagination.</SylvieRace_Cheongsam.description>
  <SylvieRace_SpringFestivalWedding.label>Spring Festival Wedding</SylvieRace_SpringFestivalWedding.label>
  <SylvieRace_SpringFestivalWedding.description>This outfit seems to have been made to celebrate an ancient festival; its fiery red color always draws one's gaze irresistibly.</SylvieRace_SpringFestivalWedding.description>
  <SylvieRace_PurpleDress.label>Purple Dress</SylvieRace_PurpleDress.label>
  <SylvieRace_PurpleDress.description>The seductive purple is always captivating and unforgettable. Its fluffy texture gives it a feeling entirely different from that of the black dress, making one yearn to catch a glimpse of the person beneath it.</SylvieRace_PurpleDress.description>
  <SylvieRace_BlueDress.label>Blue Dress</SylvieRace_BlueDress.label>
  <SylvieRace_BlueDress.description>A light blue, elegant dress with a refined aura — it must look quite lovely when worn.</SylvieRace_BlueDress.description>
  <SylvieRace_FloralDress.label>Floral Dress</SylvieRace_FloralDress.label>
  <SylvieRace_FloralDress.description>It carries a rich summer atmosphere, giving an exceptionally refreshing feeling.</SylvieRace_FloralDress.description>
  <SylvieRace_ElegantClothingPants.label>Elegant Clothing Pants</SylvieRace_ElegantClothingPants.label>
  <SylvieRace_ElegantClothingPants.description>Elegant clothing pants.</SylvieRace_ElegantClothingPants.description>
  <SylvieRace_StudentUniformPants.label>Student Uniform Pants</SylvieRace_StudentUniformPants.label>
  <SylvieRace_StudentUniformPants.description>Student uniform pants.</SylvieRace_StudentUniformPants.description>
  <SylvieRace_SpringFestivalHeadwear.label>Spring Festival Headwear</SylvieRace_SpringFestivalHeadwear.label>
  <SylvieRace_SpringFestivalHeadwear.description>A spring festival headwear.</SylvieRace_SpringFestivalHeadwear.description>
  <SylvieRace_Bandaid.label>Bandaid</SylvieRace_Bandaid.label>
  <SylvieRace_Bandaid.description>Who on earth came up with the idea of using band-aids as clothing? How is this any different from being completely naked?</SylvieRace_Bandaid.description>
  <SylvieRace_Swimsuit.label>Swimsuit</SylvieRace_Swimsuit.label>
  <SylvieRace_Swimsuit.description>It's just an ordinary swimsuit, yet it never fails to set one's pulse racing.</SylvieRace_Swimsuit.description>
  <SylvieRace_Shawl.label>Shawl</SylvieRace_Shawl.label>
  <SylvieRace_Shawl.description>A shawl.</SylvieRace_Shawl.description>
  <SylvieRace_NurseUniform.label>Nurse uniform</SylvieRace_NurseUniform.label>
  <SylvieRace_NurseUniform.description>A work-oriented nurse uniform made of delicate silk that gives a sense of reassurance. Through the thin fabric, one can faintly make out a slender figure beneath. It seems to have a peculiar effect on wearer.</SylvieRace_NurseUniform.description>
  <SylvieRace_SuitsPants.label>Suits Pants</SylvieRace_SuitsPants.label>
  <SylvieRace_SuitsPants.description>Suits pants that match the formal suit jacket.</SylvieRace_SuitsPants.description>
  <SylvieRace_Steampunk.label>Steampunk</SylvieRace_Steampunk.label>
  <SylvieRace_Steampunk.description>The armor-like clothes that only noble lords could afford were more like a suit of armor than actual garments. The built-in steam system could endow the wearer with a more powerful physique. The high-tech of the nobility enabled the armor to have an auxiliary aiming system, allowing the wearer to aim more precisely. The thick armor could defend against the vast majority of attacks. However, this armor was not fireproof, and due to its huge size, it was almost impossible to do other work. Logically speaking, commoners could not own such things. Perhaps it had been sold on the black market after the bankruptcy of that noble.</SylvieRace_Steampunk.description>
</LanguageData>
